#### Contact

dbarnhill001@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/david-barnhill-a9a294ab (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

ER/Trauma
Ultrasound guided IV access
Healthcare

# **David Barnhill**

RN, BSN, CEN Cardiac Cath Lab/Emergency Department Porter, Texas

### Summary

I am an experienced Registered Nurse in acute and emergent care settings who maintains certifications in BLS, ACLS, PALS, TNCC, ENPC, ABLS, NRP, S.T.A.B.L.E. Additionally, I am certified by the BCEN and hold an active compact license in my home state of Texas and an active license in Louisiana. My specialty is focussed on Cardiac Cath Lab and Electrophysiology with a background in ER, Trauma, and critical care.

## Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System 6 years 1 month

Registered Nurse Cardiac Cath Lab June 2017 - Present (3 years)

Registered Nurse ER/Trauma May 2014 - Present (6 years 1 month)

Texas Emergency Care Center Emergency Room Registered Nurse March 2015 - Present (5 years 3 months)

PRN Registered Nurse at full service free standing Emergency Care Center.

#### Education

Northwestern State University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2015 - 2017)

Northwestern State University
Associates Degree in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2007 - 2009)